resumup.com 2018-10-11

# ResumUP.com | Privacy Policy

At New Recruiting Solutions, Inc. we concerned about your privacy. By visiting the Resumup.com website (the "Website"), submitting information or using any of our services, or creating an account to use Resumup.com, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy covers Resumup.com's treatment of personally identifiable information (collectively with "Submitted Information" (as defined herein), the "Personal Information") that Resumup.com gathers when you are accessing the Website and when you use the Resumup.com Service or register for a Resumup.com Account. Furthermore, this Privacy Policy covers Resumup.com's treatment of any Personal Information that Resumup.com's business partners share with Resumup.com. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Resumup.com does not own or control, or to individuals that Resumup.com does not employ or manage.

The types of Personal Information collected may include your full name, e-mail address, blog or other personal website URL and any other information that would allow Resumup.com to identify you or contact you if needed.

In addition to the Personal Information mentioned, we may ask you to provide certain other information such as general demographic information, including age, gender, ZIP code, preferences, and interests. The information we gather from our users enables us to personalize and improve the Resumup.com Service.

We may receive and store any information you enter on the Website or provide to us in any other way. The Personal Information you provide may be used for providing attribution to comments you post, to operate and improve the Website, and to better deliver the Resumup.com Service.

By registering for a Resumup.com Account, you may have the option to sign in using third party social networking websites (collectively, the "Social Networks"), such as Facebook or LinkedIn or others. If you choose to sign in through these Social Networks, we use the information you have already provided to such Social Networks in registering for an account with such Social Networks and which you have allowed such Social Networks to share with Resumup.com, including, but not limited to, your first name, your user profile picture, your friends and contacts list, and the networks to which you belong (collectively, your "Submitted Information").

You expressly authorize us to collect and use your Submitted Information in connection with your use of the Resumup.com Services. You further acknowledge and agree that Resumup.com may, but is not obligated to, maintain copies of your Submitted Information indefinitely, or delete any or all Submitted Information, at our sole discretion.

We may receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with the Website and/or Resumup.com Service. Resumup.com may choose to automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you requested.

You have the right to assign to your personal page a short (sub-domain) name replacing the id ordinal number for web addressing purposes. The sub-domain name cannot be selected from the words and names the use of which is prohibited in accordance with these Terms, legislation and international legal acts, including without limitation obscene words, names registered as trademarks, brand names and commercial designations, unless you are their exclusive owner. We reserve the right to remove or reclaim any user sub-domain name if we believe it is appropriate.

Except as described in this Privacy Policy, your personal information will be used only by Resumup.com and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates, and your personal information will not be disclosed to any other third party without your consent.

Resumup.com occasionally hires other companies to provide limited administrative and communication services on our behalf, such as hosting websites, the processing and delivery of mailings, providing customer support, or performing statistical analysis of the Services. Those companies will be permitted to obtain only such personal information as necessary for them to deliver the service. Those companies are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using it for any other purpose. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information for the above purposes.

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that are transferred. Moreover, if Resumup.com, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Resumup.com may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

Resumup.com may access and/or disclose personal information about you or your account without your prior consent if Resumup.com has a good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (i) comply with legal process or other legal requirements of any governmental authority; (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of Resumup.com (including the enforcement of our agreements); (iii) enforce the Terms of Use, which can be accessed at Resumup.com/terms (v) operate or conduct maintenance and repair of the Services or equipment as authorized by law; or (vi) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Resumup.com Services or members of the public.

We maintain reasonable standards of security and confidentiality and store Personal Information collected in a database. However, while we employ reasonable standards of security, no security system is impenetrable. For most internet sites, it is possible that third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions you submit. As such, Resumup.com cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won’t be intercepted while being transmitted to Resumup.com over the internet. We recommend that you do not disclose your password or confirmation number (as applicable) to anyone.

Upon registration for events and/or services provided by Resumup.com, we may send you daily or weekly e-mails. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please notify us by e-mail at info@resumup.com and include sufficient information for us to identify your account, including your name, email address and the specifics of your request. However, after you unsubscribe to cease receiving e-mails, Resumup.com may still contact you via e-mail for administrative or informational purposes, including messages regarding the administration of your account and/or any services or events to which you have registered.

This website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an enquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the Resumup.com website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.

Resumup.com may allow third-party ad serving companies, including ad networks, to display advertisements on the Website. Ad serving companies may place a persistent cookie on your computer in order to recognize your computer each time they display an online advertisement to you, and as such, they may be able to compile information over time about whether you reviewed or clicked on advertisements they display. These companies may use this information to display targeted advertisements and may associate this information with your subsequent visits, purchases or other activities on participating advertisers’ websites.

Resumup.com retains the discretion to amend or modify this Privacy Policy from time to time, in its sole discretion. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected. If we make changes in the way we use your Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the Website, and such changes shall be effective immediately upon posting. You agree to review this Privacy Policy periodically to ensure that you are aware of any changes. Your continued access or use of the Website and/or the Resumup.com Service shall be deemed your conclusive acceptance of any amendments and/or modifications.

Resumup.com welcomes any questions or comments you may have regarding this Privacy Policy or if you do not understand any information about how we collect, maintain, use, or share your Personal Information. Any such questions or comments should be submitted via email to info@resumup.com. We will make every effort to resolve or answer your concern.

Resumup.com MAY MODIFY THIS PRIVACY NOTICE AT ANY TIME, IN RESUMUP.COM’S SOLE DISCRETION, AND SUCH MODIFICATION SHALL BE EFFECTIVE IMMEDIATELY UPON EITHER POSTING OF THE MODIFIED PRIVACY NOTICE ON THE WEBSITE OR NOTIFYING YOU. YOU AGREE TO REVIEW THIS PRIVACY NOTICE PERIODICALLY TO ENSURE THAT YOU ARE AWARE OF ANY MODIFICATIONS. YOUR CONTINUED ACCESS OR USE OF THE WEBSITE AND/OR THE SOFTWARE SHALL BE DEEMED YOUR CONCLUSIVE ACCEPTANCE OF THE MODIFIED PRIVACY NOTICE.

Effective date: February 14, 2014.
